[
    [
        {
            "question": "Type the letter 'a'.",
            "answers": ["a", "A"]
        },
        {
            "question": "Type the letter 'b'.",
            "answers": ["b", "B"]
        },
        {
            "question": "Type the letter 'c'.",
            "answers": ["c", "C"]
        },
        {
            "question": "Type the letter 'd'.",
            "answers": ["d", "D"]
        },
        {
            "question": "Type the letter 'e'.",
            "answers": ["e", "E"]
        },
        {
            "question": "Type the letter 'f'.",
            "answers": ["f", "F"]
        },
        {
            "question": "Type the letter 'g'.",
            "answers": ["g", "G"]
        },
        {
            "question": "Type the letter 'h'.",
            "answers": ["h", "H"]
        },
        {
            "question": "Type the letter 'i'.",
            "answers": ["i", "I"]
        },
        {
            "question": "Type the letter 'j'.",
            "answers": ["j", "J"]
        }
    ],
    [
        {
            "question": "What is 1+1?",
            "answers": ["2", "11", "1+1", "1 + 1", "1+ 1", "1 +1"]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 2+2?",
            "answers": ["4", "22", "2+2", "2 + 2", "2+ 2", "2 +2"]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 3+3?",
            "answers": ["6", "33", "3+3", "3 + 3", "3+ 3", "3 +3"]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 4+4?",
            "answers": ["8", "44", "4+4", "4 + 4", "4+ 4", "4 +4"]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 5+5?",
            "answers": ["10", "55", "5+5", "5 + 5", "5+ 5", "5 +5"]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 6+6?",
            "answers": ["12", "66", "6+6", "6 + 6", "6+ 6", "6 +6"]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 7+7?",
            "answers": ["14", "77", "7+7", "7 + 7", "7+ 7", "7 +7"]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 8+8?",
            "answers": ["16", "88", "8+8", "8 + 8", "8+ 8", "8 +8"]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 9+9?",
            "answers": ["18", "99", "9+9", "9 + 9", "9+ 9", "9 +9"]
        }
    ],
    [
        {
            "question": "What color do you get if you mix red and yellow?",
            "answers": ["orange", "Orange"]
        },
        {
            "question": "What color do you get if you mix red and green?",
            "answers": ["brown", "Brown", "yellow", "Yellow"]
        },
        {
            "question": "What color do you get if you mix blue and red?",
            "answers": ["violet", "Violet", "purple", "Purple", "magenta", "Magenta"]
        },
        {
            "question": "What color do you get if you mix black and white?",
            "answers": ["gray", "Gray", "grey", "Gray"]
        },
        {
            "question": "What color do you get if mix white and red?",
            "answers": ["pink", "Pink"]
        },
        {
            "question": "What color do you get if you mix yellow and violet?",
            "answers": ["black", "Black", "white", "White"]
        },
        {
            "question": "What color do you get if you mix red with red?",
            "answers": ["red", "Red", "Uh...red?"]
        },
        {
            "question": "What color do you get if you mix all of the colors together?",
            "answers": ["black", "Black", "white", "White"]
        }
    ],
    [
        {
            "question": "What is the country that borders the USA to the north?",
            "answers": ["Canada", "canada", "CA", "ca"]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the second largest country in the world?",
            "answers": ["Canada", "canada", "CA", "ca"]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the country that exports the most maple syrup?",
            "answers": ["Canada", "canada", "CA", "ca"]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the country has a province named 'Quebec'?",
            "answers": ["Canada", "canada", "CA", "ca"]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the country that has the largest coastline in the world?",
            "answers": ["Canada", "canada", "CA", "ca"]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the country that contains over half of all the world's lakes?",
            "answers": ["Canada", "canada", "CA", "ca"]
        },
        {
            "question": "Ottawa is the capital city of what country?",
            "answers": ["Canada", "canada", "CA", "ca"]
        },
        {
            "question": "What does 'C-A-N-A-D-A' spell?",
            "answers": ["Canada", "canada", "C-A-N-A-D-A", "c-a-n-a-d-a"]
        }
    ],
    [
        {
            "question": "Johannes Gutenberg revolutionized the spread of information with his invention of the _________.",
            "answers": ["printing press", "Printing Press", "Printing press"]
        },
        {
            "question": "Charles Babbage is often credited as being the first person to conceive the __________.",
            "answers": ["computer", "Computer"]
        },
        {
            "question": "Boy scientist Jimmy Neutron invented his own pet! A dog named _________.",
            "answers": ["Goddard"]
        },
        {
            "question": "Thomas Edison's rival, _________, invented alternating current.",
            "answers": ["Tesla", "Nikola Tesla", "Nikola"]
        },
        {
            "question": "Alexander Graham Bell helpe us connect a little easier by inventing the first _________.",
            "answers": ["phone", "Phone", "telelphone", "Telephone"]
        },
        {
            "question": "Thomas Edison is known for inventing the _________.",
            "answers": ["lightbulb", "Lightbulb", "light bulb", "Light Bulb", "Light bulb", "light globes"]
        }
    ],
    [
        {
            "question": "Every cell is enclosed by a cell _________ that acts as the cell's wall.",
            "answers": ["membrane", "Membrane"]
        },
        {
            "question": "The _________ is the control center of the cell that holds the DNA.",
            "answers": ["nucleus", "Nucleus"]
        },
        {
            "question": "The _________ is known as the 'power house' of the cell as it produces energy using glucose and oxygen.",
            "answers": ["something", "Something"]
        },
        {
            "question": "The _________ in cells help link amino acids together to form proteins.",
            "answers": ["ribosome", "Ribosome"]
        },
        {
            "question": "The _________ is a dense region in the nucleus of a cell that is made up of RNA.",
            "answers": ["nucleolus", "Nucleolus"]
        }
    ],
    [
        {
            "question": "The classic progressive rock band _________ released it's album In the Court of the Crimson King in 1969.",
            "answers": ["King Crimson"]
        },
        {
            "question": "The Beatles released their 9th studio album in 1968. It had no graphic on the record sleeve, giving it the nickname _________.",
            "answers": ["the white album", "The White Album", "The white album"]
        },
        {
            "question": "Radiohead took a stylistic left turn with their 4th studio album _________. It received mixed reception at the time, but is now seen as a cultural influence for electronic music.",
            "answers": ["Kid A", "Kid a", "kid a"]
        },
        {
            "question": "Something",
            "answers": ["something", "Something"]
        }
    ],
    [
        {
            "question": "What would be the highest of the three notes of an augmented G chord?",
            "answers": ["d#", "D#", "d sharp", "D sharp", "D Sharp"]
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of the three notes in a major triad would you have to shift to make it minor? The lower, the middle, or the higher note?",
            "answers": ["middle", "Middle", "middle note", "Middle Note", "the middle", "The Middle", "The middle", "the middle note", "The Middle Note", "The middle note", "third", "the third", "Third", "The Third"]
        },
        {
            "question": "The major scale is also known as the _________ mode. ",
            "answers": ["ionian", "Ionian"]
        }
    ],
    [
        {
            "question": "What is the antiderivate of f(x)=1/x ? [Do not type any spaces in your answer.]",
            "answers": ["lnx", "ln|x|", "ln(x)", "ln(|x|)", "f(x)=ln(x)", "F(x)=ln(x)", "f(x)=ln(|x|)", "F(x)=ln(|x|)", "ln(x)+C", "ln(|x|)+C", "f(x)=ln(x)+C", "F(x)=ln(x)+C", "f(x)=ln(|x|)+C", "F(x)=ln(|x|)+C", "ln(x)+c", "ln(|x|)+c", "f(x)=ln(x)+c", "F(x)=ln(x)+c", "f(x)=ln(|x|)+c", "F(x)=ln(|x|)+c"]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the infinite sum of the series 4 - 4/3 + 4/5 - 4/7 + 4/9 - ... ?",
            "answers": ["pi", "Pi", "PI", "3.14", "3.142", "3.1415", "Ï€"]
        }
    ],
    [
        {
            "question": "What number was Justin Rittenhouse thinking of when he wrote this question?",
            "answers": ["0.1"]
        }
    ]
]